hi everyone and welcome to new every day
新しい毎日 の 皆さん、こんにちは 、ウェルカム
my name is Kari my name is Jen and have
私の名前は 私の名前はジェンと 持って いる カリ であります
you ever once punched someone in the
あなたは今まで一度 に 誰かを殴っ
throat well on this show we just say
この番組でよく喉
hashtag today no to throw punching we
今日はハッシュタグを付けない でください
will be right back
戻ってきます
this is new every day with Jen wagger
これはジェンwagger で 毎日新しいです
and Gary Webb
とゲイリーウェッブ
[Music]
[音楽]
hi thanks for tuning back into new
こんにちは新しいに戻って調整していただきありがとうございます
everyday we're so glad that you have
毎日私たちはあなたが持っていることをとても嬉しく思います
tuned in and we have been talking about
に調整し、私たちは話してきました
all of these great life hacks Jen from
これらの素晴らしい人生のすべてがJenからハックされます
the book of Proverbs specifically having
特に持っている ことわざ の本
to do with communication yes first one
コミュニケーションをするためにはい
is listening and why is listening
聞いているとなぜ聞いている
important because it's how you hear
それはあなたが聞く方法だから重要だ
thanks nice if you don't listen you
あなたが あなたを 聞い て いない場合は ありがとう ございました
aren't going to hear what the other
他 にどのような聞きするつもりはありません
person says and you're thinking yes that
人は言う 、あなたはそう考えている
is true
本当です
so that was a good answer a it was a
それは良い答えでした
great answer thank you so much Jeanine
偉大な答えありがとう そんなに ジェニーン
helps us to actually hear what the other
実際に相手の 声を聞きやすくします。
person is saying and you wait to the
人が 言っている と あなたは
other person is finished huh and then
他の人はハァッそしてそれから 終わる
you speak so week number two was choose
あなたはとても話す週 2が選ばれました
to be kind and why is choosing no I
親切にし、なぜ私を選ばないのか
answer the first one why is choosing to
最初のものに答える
be kind
親切にする
choosing to be kind is important so that
親切にすることが重要です
our words don't come out in manipulation
私たちの言葉は改ざんされていません
or control or like a harsh way or harsh
または制御または厳しい方法や厳しいのように
word because that crushes that crushes
単語それが押しつぶすため押しつぶすこと
our spirits so and when we choose to be
私たちの霊はそうと、私たちは あること を選択した場合
kind then it's not it really is not
親切じゃないですか
about getting our own way what we're
自分のやり方 を 自分たちの ものにすることについて
wanting the very best for the other
他の人に最高のものを望んでいる
person mm-hmm so that's why it's
人mm-hmmだから、それが理由です
important to be choose to be kind in our
私たちに親切にすることを選択することが重要
words and I think we also need to choose
言葉と私 たちも 選択する必要がある と思い ます
to be honest which was last week yes oh
正直言って、先週だったそうです
yes and it's so we discussed that is so
はい、 それはそう私たちが議論したのでそうです
hard to be honest because it reflects
それが反映されているので正直に言うのは難しい
what's going on in our own heart yeah
私たち自身の心の中で何が起こっているのか
and well if I'm honest will they still
そして正直なところ、彼らはまだ
accept me if I'm honest well they still
正直言って も 私を受け入れて
want to be my friend if I'm honest you
私はあなたが正直なら私の友達に なりたい です。
know and they might gonna have to walk
知っていて、 彼らは歩かなければならないかもしれません
with them through whatever they're going
彼らが行っているものは何でも を通して 彼らと
through or more the accountability yes
説明責任を通じて、またはそれ以上
yeah and we also said choosing not to
ええと私たちはまたしないことを選択した
say anything is being dishonest anyways
とにかく不正を言っている
even though you haven't said any words
何も言っていないのに
by choosing not to say words so it
それようの言葉を言っていない 選択することにより、
protects you is still being dishonest
あなたがたを守ることはまだ不正直である
so that brings us to this week and we
だから今週に私たちをもたらします
said that this week we're talking about
今週話し ている
choosing to be patient
辛抱強く選ぶ
or hashtag say no throw punches right
またはハッシュタグは、投げ捨てない 権利を 言う
because it's so easy when somebody says
誰かが言うととても簡単だから
something and you just want to haul off
何か、あなたはただ 引き取り たい
and be like I would ever get anyone I
そして私は今まで私が 誰か に なるだろうよう に
just can't even imagine you doing that
想像もできません
like I just don't even know what my
私は私のことさえ分からない
response would be I'm cat bit me once
返事は私が猫私が一度私を噛んだことでしょう
and I threw it oh because it literally
そして、私は ので、それは文字通り ああ 、それを投げました
bit me and I'm like BAM when I threw it
私を噛んで投げた とき は BAMみたい だ
because that Oh reflex action okay
その あリフレックスアクション大丈夫 ため、
because when we talk about no throat
喉がないと話すとき
punch right to talk about being patient
忍耐強いことについて話す権利
what happens often with with words and
言葉でよく起こること
communication somebody can say something
誰かが言うことができるコミュニケーション
and there's a reaction and there's a
そして 反応 があり、
reacts very visceral when the cat hit me
猫が私を襲ったときに非常に内臓に反応します
like bit me it hurt the word that quite
私のようにそれはかなりその単語を傷つけた
hurt and so it was immediate right and
傷ついたのですぐに正しかった
so sometimes when those words those
時々 これらの言葉
words can come in we immediately say
言葉がすぐに出てくる
yeah but you're stupid or yeah you know
そうだけど、 あなたはばかだ か知っている
you would say that if you you know you
あなたがあれば、あなたは あなたを 知っていると言うでしょう
weren't so ugly like oh right because
ああそんなに醜くなかったので
because and we talked about this before
と 私たちは前にこれについて話した ので
the words often come out of what's on
言葉はしばしば何があるのか​​から出てくる
the inside yes and so when another it
中 はい そして そう また 別の時それ
comes so we're just going to use this
私たちはただ 、これを 使用するつもりきます
the hurt comes because this is the sign
これがサインだから痛い
for the cat but I need your hand and you
猫のために私は あなたの手とあなた が必要 です
want to just throw it because it hurt
それが痛いので ちょうど それを 投げたい
yeah it hurt and sometimes it's I did
うん、それは痛いし、 時にはそれは私がやった
not expect the cat to bite me right like
猫が私のように噛むのを期待してはいけない
I was petting it this is not a story
私はそれをかわいがっていた これは 物語で はありません
about cats but I was petting it
猫についてですが、私はそれをかわいがっていました
obviously it is maybe and it bit me I
明らかにそれは多分それは私 を 噛んだ
was not expecting it and it hurt and so
それを期待していなかったし、それが痛いので
my immediate immediate response was to
私の即時の即時応答をしました
literally throw the cat which is true in
文字通り真実である猫を投げる
communication so if you if you are not
そうでなければコミュニケーション
expecting the response and then you're
応答を期待して、あなたは
hurt by it and then I think Jen like
それによって傷ついて、それから私はジェンが好きだと思う
there is a place there when the lord
主がいるときにそこに場所がある
says like the Bible says don't take
聖書のように 言わないで
offense like it might hurt but I'm gonna
それが傷つくかもしれないような犯罪 が私はつもりだ
choose not to be offended right and tell
正しく 気分を害さないように選択して伝える
myself like the Lord is my defense I
私のように私は主のように私の防衛です 私は
don't need to defend myself like that
その ように自分自身を守る必要はありません
mm-hmm
mm-hmm
because a hot-tempered man and this
暑い人とこれが
comes from Proverbs 1429 you just have a
箴言1429から来た
little bit of a teleprompter over here
テレプロンプターのほんの少し
so tell me 15 ok yes 14 29 and also
だから私に言って15 OKはい14 29そしてまた
proverbs 15 18 so I'll read proverbs 15
箴言15 18箴言15を読むので
18 ok 9 ok a patient man has great
18 [OK] 9 [OK] 患者の男は偉大あり
understanding but a quick tempered man
理解しているが、素早い人
displays folly and that actually a folly
愚か者を表示し、それは実際には愚か者です。
is basically they don't know any better
基本的に彼らはそれ以上良く知らない
hmm they don't only have a desire for
うーん、欲しいだけ じゃない
for peace or the follies like getting
平和のため に
into trouble and so a quick temper man
トラブルに遭遇したので素早い気性の男
is going to get into trouble whereas the
一方、 トラブルに取得する予定です
patient man is going to just be like
患者の男は、 同じ よう になるだろう
like that's going to calm down and be at
落ち着いている ように
peace can you walk around throat
平和は喉の周りを歩くことができます
punching all the time you're not gonna
あなたがするつもりはないすべての時間をパンチング
make friends I think that's the moral
友達を作ることが道徳だと思う
the story yeah this is they have a great
物語ええ これは彼らが素晴らしいを持っているということです
understanding patient man has great
忍耐強い人を理解することは素晴らしい
understanding so those those words can
それらの言葉ができるように理解する
come in and even though you didn't
入ってきて
expect it or yet hurt patients is and we
それを期待するか、それでも 患者を 傷つける と
talked about this just recently patience
この 最近の忍耐について話しました
isn't about walking often there's
およそ しばしば あります 歩いていません
respons lesions is living out the best
責任 病変は最もうまく生きている
of what God has in the moment is really
瞬間は本当に神が持っているもの
what patience is it's not about well I'm
忍耐力って何 じゃよく ない
not going to react I'm not going to do
私は やるつもり はありません反応するつもりはありません
that I'm going to wait patience is while
辛抱して待つのはしばらく
I'm waiting or instead of responding
私は待っているか の 代わりに、 応答しています
quickly I'm going to basically bring God
すぐに 私は基本的に神をもたらすつもりです
into the moment and live out this one
現時点ではこれを生きる
it's the very best of what it can be
それはそれができる ものの 非常に ベストです
rather than responding quickly or just
迅速にあるいは単に反応するのではなく
trying to pass time so patience is
時間をかけようとする ので忍耐は
emilie very thoughts it says it's a
エミリー はそれが
fruit of the Spirit so in this moment I
この瞬間、私は御霊の実です
need the fruit of the Spirit I need the
霊の実が必要です
Holy Spirit to birth in me joy and
聖霊が私の中に生まれる喜びと
goodness and
良さと
faithfulness you know self-control in
あなたが 自制心 を知っている忠実さ
patience patience is so often when you
忍耐忍耐はとても頻繁 に
say well I'm praying for patience well
よく言う私は忍耐をよく祈っている
then you're praying for opportunities to
それからあなたは機会を祈っています
experience the goodness of God in
で神の善を体験する
not-so-great situations sometimes and so
それほど素晴らしい状況ではないこともあります
when it says you know maybe man has
それはあなたが多分人が持っていることを知っていると言うとき
great understanding they realize that
彼らはそれを理解している
instead of responding so quickly but
迅速 に 対応する代わりに
they just need to take that moment and
彼らはただその 瞬間 を取る必要が あります
maybe wait on the Lord to think twice to
二度 考えるように主を待ちなさい
be slow to speak so that they don't have
彼らが持っていない ように話すの が遅い
clean-up on aisle nine yeah because a
通路 9のクリーンアップええ ので、
quick time for man not only is it the
男性のための迅速な時間がないだけ です
throat punch to you know to that other
あなたに喉のパンチは 、他に 知っ ている
person but then they man I'm so sorry
人がそれから彼らは男すみません
I'm sorry I should I shouldn't have hit
すみません、ヒットしてはいけません。
you well why did you hit while it was
あなたはなぜ それがあっ た のにあなた はなぜ ヒットしましたか
just bottling up inside me well do you
私の中に瓶詰めするだけ
think you should work that out well yeah
うまく いくはずだと思う
maybe I should spend some time getting
多分私は得るのにしばらく時間を費やすべきです
out in a more healthy way these are on
より健康的な 方法 で
the inside is there quality life skills
中に は 質の高い ライフスキル があり ます
they are often I will tell people if
彼ら はしばしば 私が 人々 に伝えます
you're angry like deal with it like deal
あなたは 取引のように それを扱うように 怒っています
with it whether it's you know scribbling
それはあなたが落書きを知っているかどうかそれで
on a piece of paper to get because with
一枚 の紙に
emotions there is an energy associated
関連するエネルギーがある 感情
with it that has to be expressed in a
それ と で 表現されなければならないことを
physical way that's why I often with
なぜ 、多くの場合で の物理的な方法
grief and sadness the physical response
悲しみと悲しみの物理的な応答
is this use my unique we need to leak we
これは私たちがリークする必要がある私のユニークな使用です
need to leave it's like it meets up with
それが会うようなものであることを去る必要がある
all that energy that's on the inside and
内側にあるすべてのエネルギー
then it spills it down the front of our
それからそれ は私たち の 正面に それをこぼし ます
face so tears are so important when
顔が涙でとても大切なとき
you're angry like a physical response
あなたは 身体的反応のように 怒っています
would be like like even saying I'm so
私もそう言っているようなものです
angry and you throw your arms down like
怒って、 あなたは腕を下ろす
it's that physical response or I'd like
それはその物理的な反応か私が欲しいのです
to think like if you're a woodchopper go
あなたがウッドチョッパーであるかのように考えるために
and chop wood if you need to go for a
あなたがのために行く必要がある場合は 、 木材を切り刻みます
run then you go for a run our parents
走って、あなたは 私たちの両親の 走りに行きます
have told me that's why they like a long
それが彼らが長いのが好きな理由だと私に言った
commute oh yeah if something decompress
何か解凍したら通勤
work then they can decompress and so
作業後、彼らは解凍し、そうすることができます
they come into the house and they're
彼らは家に入ってくる
ready so they've had time to decompress
準備ができたので解凍する時間がありました
but they said actually when you live
あなたが住んでいるときしかし彼らは実際に言った
close to home and you only have like a
家の近くであなたは
five minute commute home it's on their
5分通勤の家にいます
home and everybody's on there yeah
家と誰もがそう そこにあります
it's where you've had no
それはあなたがい なかった ところです
so even though all those emotions are
それでも、 これらの感情 は すべて
bottled up you have no time to actually
瓶詰めあなたは 実際に 時間がない
process them yeah that's true need time
それらを処理する
to price these well you've gone on so
これらの 値段を 付ける ために 、 これ まで行って きた
that's why it says a patient man has
それはそれが忍耐強い人が持っていると言う理由です
very understanding but a quick tempered
非常に理解していますが 、素早い
man like it'll lead to folly because you
それのような男は愚かにつながりますので、 ご
they're quick because they haven't had
彼らは 持っていなかったので 彼らは速いです
time they're responding out of what has
彼らが持っているものから彼らが応答している時
happened yes right yep rather than
そうではなくて
that's why if somebody's had a really
誰かが本当に持っていたら
good day all of a sudden you get really
あなたが 本当に 得る突然のすべての良い日
good responses from them in your life
あなたの生活の 中 で 彼らからの 良い反応
Wow you've had a good day because we
われわれが 良い日を過ごしたなんて
respond out of what has happened to us
私たちに起こったことから返答する
so if we haven't had a good day if some
もし私たちが良い日を過ごしていなければ
stuff happened at the office and you're
オフィスで何かが起こったし、 あなたは
not in a good frame sometimes it is
良いフレームではありません
easier just to say I can't talk right
私は正しく話すことができないと言うためだけに簡単
now I need five minutes and and
今、 私は5分必要です
sometimes I will just I'll go into my
時々 私は私が私のに入るよ
room or something will happen that'll
部屋や何かが起こるでしょう
just hurt me and I'll have to it very
ただ私を傷つけると私はそれをする必要があります
obscure men are like Laura I actually
あいまいな男性は 実は ローラ 私の ようなものです
find this upsetting it has nothing to do
この動揺を見つけても意味がありません
that other person is because I know I'm
他の人 は私が知っているからです
hurt on the inside and their words
内側とその言葉を傷つける
weren't hurtful but I could because of
害はありませんでした が
my own hair and the inside mind you
私自身の髪と内側の 心あなた
respond I don't know if I want to say
私が 言い たい場合 、私は 知らない 対応
past hurt so Carrie could very easily
過去のけがをしたのでキャリーはとても簡単に
say something to me that is not unkind
不親切 では ない何かを私に言う
or untruthful it's just a statement but
それとも単なる陳述ですが
because of my own hurt that I haven't
私がしていないことが自分のせいで
dealt with yet my response could come
まだ 対処 した
out very angry and you could be thinking
非常に怒ってあなたが考えている可能性があります
why is she responding this way which is
なぜ彼女は このよう に 反応しているの か
bad for communication because then she's
それでコミュニケーションに悪い
not going to want to share things with
共有 したくない
me because she doesn't know how I'm
彼女は私がどうやってわからないので私は
going to respond and that then that
それに応えよう
leads to rejection and you know lack of
拒絶反応につながり、 あなたは
acceptance and because we actually don't
受け入れ、私たちは 実際にはそうではないので
deal with the stuff on the inside and so
内部にものを扱うので、
I often find myself saying Lord what
私はしばしば自分自身を 主に 言っているのを見つけます
that person said was not unkind was not
その人は不親切ではないとは言わなかった
hurtful was not anything I mean
私にとって何も悪いことではありませんでした
responding about a veneer of rejection
拒絶の単板について反応する
my own fear of mistrust my own whatever
不信の私自身の恐怖私自身 何でも
I'm respond so or I can feel that in my
私はそう反応する か、私は私の中でそれを感じることができる
heart would you brace
心はあなたがブレースでしょうか
there because I don't want to respond in
私は応答したくないのでそこに
a way yeah that is going to be quick
それが 迅速になるだろう ええ方法
time quick temper or like a throat punch
時間の早さやスロートパンチのような
I don't want to respond that way because
私はその よう に反応したくない ので
that's not helpful that's not truthful
それは有用ではないそれは真実ではない
and yes I could be sad about something
はい、 私は何かに悲しいことができます
or upset or angry it has absolutely
絶対に動揺しているか怒っている
nothing to do with that person because
ので、 その人と は何の関係もありません
they've actually said everything that's
彼らは実際に すべてを 言った
right and you know in keeping with that
それに合わせ て 知っ ている
Jen I think where patience comes in as
Jen 私 は忍耐力がどこに入ってくると思います
like this communication pearl is that
このコミュニケーションパールのようなものです
after you've asked the Lord I don't want
望まない主に尋ねた後
to respond this way help me then it
このように答えることはそれから私を助けます
takes patience to actually trust that he
実際に彼を信頼する ため に忍耐を取る
can equip you to do it if we've been
私たち がされ て いる 場合はそれを行うためにあなたを装備することができます
given everything we need for life and
私たちは 生活の ために必要なすべてを与えられ、
godliness then to actually like apply
それから実際に好きなように信心深さ
faith to that ask that I can wait and
それへの信仰は私が待つことができることを尋ねる
not have to respond right away or not
すぐに返答する 必要はない
have to respond and kind like the
応答し、のように親切にする必要が あります
patience is in the waiting yeah you know
忍耐が待機中であるええ 、あなたは知っています
yes so we're gonna ask you to be patient
はい、辛抱強くお願いします
and wait for us until we come back from
私たち が戻ってくるまで 待って
this message
このメッセージ
[Music]
[音楽]
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
ThinkGeekギアベストで買い物をするかどうか
B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon or even
B&amp;Hの写真ビデオのeBayやAmazon 、さらには
if you want a free trial of audible
あなたが聞こえるの無料試用版が欲しいなら
you'll find the best deals and support
あなたは最高のお得な情報 や サポートを 見つけることができます
the shows we produce by simply visiting
我々 が単に 訪れることによって作り出すショー
the shopping sites you already frequent
あなたがすでに頻繁に訪れるショッピングサイト
by using the links on our website visit
私達のウェブサイトの訪問のリンクを使用して
category 5 TV slash partners for the
のカテゴリ5 TVスラッシュパートナー
full and ever-growing list and help us
フルと増え続けるリスト と私たちを助けます
create more free content like this show
この番組のように 無料でコンテンツを作成する
thank you for shopping with our partners
私たちのパートナーと一緒に買い物をしてくれてありがとう
and thank you for watching hey everyone
そして みんなを見てくれてありがとう
thanks for sticking with us on new every
新しい ものに 私たち と固執し てくれて ありがとう
day go to our website new every day dot
日 私たちのウェブサイトに 行く 毎日新しいドット
TV check out our partners tab and see
テレビは私達のパートナータブをチェックして見てください
the organizations and businesses that
組織や企業という
helped make this show a possibility we
この ショーを可能にするのを 手伝った
are under the umbrella of category 5
カテゴリ5の傘下にあります
they host us so when you go to support
あなたがサポートに行くとき 、彼らは そう 私たちを迎え ます
us whether it's through patreon or some
それがpatreonを通したものか、 それともいくつかのものによるものかどうか
other means you may think who is Robby
他の手段あなたは 誰が ロビー だと思う かもしれ ない
and who is category 5 well that is the
そして誰がカテゴリ5であり、それが
the network that makes this show
これを見せるネットワーク
possible and Robby is our producer
Robbyが 私たちのプロデューサーです
editor elcapitan
エディタelcapitan
who makes this show possible it's
このショーを可能にするのは誰ですか
inspirational we're very thankful so
インスピレーション、私たちはとても感謝しています
we're talking about the life hack
私たちはライフハックについて話しています
communication skills of choosing to be
であること を 選択のコミュニケーションスキル
patient Jen and it's it's not the most
患者ジェン、それはそれ が最もで はない
prolific virtue in today's society and I
今日の社会と 私 の豊かな美徳
think that in part is bred because of
部分的には 繁殖している と思う
our the instantaneous quality of so much
そんなに私たちの瞬間品質
of what we do so like I send a message I
私はメッセージIを送信する ように 、我々はそうすること の
get a message back I you know send an
返信メッセージを受け取る
email right away I want something I'm
すぐにメール、私は 私は何かを したいです
going to buy it online everything is
それをオンラインで買おうとしている
just so instantaneous that there's not a
ただ瞬間的に
necessity of being patient where I mean
私が意味する患者 であることの必要性
look it back in Pioneer days right like
パイオニア 時代に振り返ってみると
you plant the food you wait for the food
あなたは食べ物を植えるあなたは食べ物を待つ
to grow your page you have to need the
ページを大きくするには、
bread you wait for it to rise and then
パンはそれが上がるのを待ってからそれから
there's a certain joy in experiencing
経験することには確かな喜びがあります
the
の
filament of what you've been waiting for
あなたは何 を 待っていたのフィラメント
and and that might be something that
そしてそれは その何か あるかも しれません
we're missing out on oh yeah even today
私たちは今日でもおれを見逃している
we're trying to help a friend get
私たちは友達を手助けしようとしています
something fixed and we're like we want
何かが固定されていて、欲しいようなものです
it to happen now cuz they're so used to
今起きている ことは、彼らがとても慣れ親しんでいることです
things happening now absolutely and it's
今起こっていることは絶対にあり、それは
like text message hurry up and respond
テキストメッセージのように急い で応答する
or email hurry or what do you mean
または急いでEメールする、 あるいはどういう意味ですか
they're not answering the phone cuz
彼らは電話に答えていない
we're so used to that but yeah patience
我々はそれに慣れています、しかしええ忍耐
also allows the other person's heart to
相手の心にも
come into right alignment - hmm because
正しい配置になる - うーん理由
you might have you might be in the right
あなたは右にいるかもしれません
spot yourself but the other person that
自分を見つけるが他の人は それを
you're trying to communicate isn't and
あなたが コミュニケーション しようとして いるのはそうではありません
so sometimes the Lord says no just wait
だから時々 主はただ待つだけではないと言わ れる
but I have some no just wait and then I
しかし、私にはただ待つだけの ものはあり ませ ん。
gotta ask you like are you a fixer are
ダメ尋ねるあなたが好きあなたが定着 されています
you someone who hears something Oh
ああ 何かを聞いている誰か
totally and I just want to fix it I want
完全に私はちょうどそれを修正したいです
to fix the problems I want to make
私が作りたい問題を解決するために
everybody happy you want to do blah blah
誰も幸せ あなたは 何とか何とかやってみたいです
blah blah blah instead of sometimes just
たまには何もない
being patient as we were talking earlier
私達が以前に話していたよう に辛抱強く
Jen it just came to mind the the story
ジェンそれはちょうど物語を気にするようになった
of Mary in the Bible and how like the
聖書の中のマリアの
angel Gabriel came and and rocked her
天使ガブリエルが来て、そして彼女を揺り動かしました
world with the news that she's gonna
彼女はつもりだというニュースで世界
like have the Son of God in her and she
彼女の中 に神の子がいるように
carried that for nine months and things
それを9ヶ月と物のために運んだ
would happen and it says that she stored
起こるだろう、それは彼女が 保存した ことを言う
them in her heart she treasured them in
彼女の心の中で彼女はそれらを大切にしました
her heart and she was patient in waiting
彼女の心と彼女は待っていた
and knowing that God would bring to
そして 神が もたらされる ことを知っている
fulfillment everything that he had
彼が持っていたすべてを成し遂げる
promised and you don't see her like
約束してあなたは彼女が好きではない
stewing or meddling or asking too many
煮込みやめちゃくちゃにしたり、多すぎる質問
questions like there was this comma
このカンマがあったような質問
surance
倹約
and like I don't know if you can think
そして私があなたが考えることができるかどうかわからないように
of someone in your life whom you can
あなたの生活の中であなたができる 誰かの
really see this attribute as a really
この属性は本当に
salient feature in their life like what
彼らの生活の中で顕著な特徴は何のような
what are the characteristics of that
その特徴は何ですか
person and what helped to build that in
人とそれを構築するのに役立ったもの
them but can you think of a truly
彼らはあなたが 本当に 考えることができます
patient person that you can see what
何が見えるか患者さん
other aspects of their life are in check
彼らの人生の他の面はチェックされています
that they have this fruit of the Spirit
彼らがこの霊の実を持っていること
well it normally comes with listening
まあそれは通常リスニングが付属しています
well
よく
like they're willing for the other
彼らは他の人たちのため に喜んで いるように
person to finish their sentence yeah
ええ 、その文を終了する人
they listen and they choose their words
彼らは耳を傾け、彼らは自分の言葉を選びます
well before they speak right
彼らが正しく話す前に
and so this when we talk about
そしてこれは私達が話すときこれ
communication life hacks from the book
本 からコミュニケーションライフハック
of Proverbs what you really encourage
あなたが本当に励ましていることの箴言
you just to go would start reading all
あなたはただ行くだけですべてを読み始めるでしょう
the way through take your oh yeah and
通り抜けて道を
yeah okay communication and proverbs and
ええ大丈夫コミュニケーションとことわざと
just start highlighting all of them or
それら すべて を 強調表示し始めるだけです。
you don't want to highlight your Bible
聖書 を強調したくない
go online and type in communication
オンラインにしてコミュニケーションをタイプする
verses and proverbs oh yeah and so like
詩と箴言 ああそうそう
a truly patient person slows down
真に忍耐強い人は減速する
actually like they and doesn't slow down
実際には彼らが好きで 遅く は ありません
like they're walking like this and
彼らはこのように歩いているように
talking like oh that's not right that's
以下のような話をすると、 ああ、それは右ではありません
not what we're saying we're saying that
我々は、我々が それを 言っている何を言っているではありません
they're slow to speak hmm and quick to
彼らはうーんと話すのが遅いです
listen mhm
うーん
that's a patient person they're willing
それは彼らが喜んでいる辛抱強い人です
to choose their words with kindness
親切に 自分の言葉を選ぶ
that's a patient person right and and
それは、 右の患者の人だとし、
they're willing to be honest but because
彼らは正直であるために喜んでいるが、理由は
they have a spirit of the Living God
彼らは生きている神の霊を持っています
inside of them then they know that
彼らの中で、彼らはそれを知っ ています
because they're willing to listen that
彼らはそれ を聞いても 構わない と 思っている から です
they're choosing their words with
彼らは彼らの言葉を選んでいます
kindness that they want to speak
彼らが話したい優しさ
honestly because of a love for another
正直なところ、別の人への愛のために
person God's gonna move in that and they
その彼ら の 人物 神のつもり動き
feel so genuine and so real hmm and
とても本物の、そして本当の うーん、そして
you're like that's what I want and so a
私が 欲しいのはそれが好きなので
patient person actually has Jesus in
忍耐強い人は実際にイエスを持っています
their life first
彼らの人生が一番
you know I first who it then works
私が最初 に知っているのはそれが誰なのか
through all these other areas to help
他のすべての分野を通じた支援
them communicate well so they do create
彼らはうまくコミュニケーションするので、彼らは創造します
this atmosphere of love and acceptance
この愛と受け入れの雰囲気
and belonging and understanding which is
そしてそれが所属し理解している
what we are all looking for so the first
我々はすべての ように最初に探し ているもの
step is always choose Jesus hmmm if you
あなたがいるならステップは常にイエス・キリスト うーんを 選ぶ ことです
want to communicate well you need to
うまくコミュニケーションをとりたい
choose Jesus and like I have to choose
イエスを選びなさいそして私が選ばなければならないように
Jesus every day cuz you might be
あなたがかもしれないcuzをイエスは毎日
thinking but I already know Jesus but
考えていますが、 私はすでにイエス様を知っていますが
are you choosing to put Jesus first
あなたはイエスを優先することを選んでいますか
every day to say lord help me to say
主を言うために毎日 私が言うのを 助け ます
what you want me to say help me to think
あなたが私に言いたいことは私が 考えるのを 助け ます
what you want me to think help me to
あなたが私 に助けてもらってほしいもの
feel what you want me to feel like bring
持ってきたい気分にさせてください
to me the people you want me to interact
私にあなたが私に対話させたい人々
with and so if you're bringing me some
一緒に持ってきてくれたら
and then I got a believe that you're
それから私はあなたがいると信じる
gonna help me you know in
あなたが知っ ている私 を 手伝うつもり です
in a really great way yeah because I've
本当に素晴らしい方法でええ私がしましたので、
invited you I've surrendered I've chosen
私が選んだ降伏した
you so we need you to we need you God
あなたは私たちがあなたを必要と する私たちはあなたを必要とする
needs you you're a person who you're
あなたはあなたがあなたがあなたである人である必要があります
speaking to needs you need to choose
あなた が選ぶ 必要が ある ニーズに話す
Jesus every day like giving him every
毎日イエス様に与えるように
day and if you have never chosen Jesus
あなたがイエスを選ばなかった日
you just sort of stumbled on our show on
あなただけの 並べ替えの上の私たちのショーにつまずい
the internet or wherever you might be
インターネットまたはどこにいても
watching it and you're like huh this
それを見て 、あなたは この ハァッ のようにしています
looks interesting this is how you choose
面白そうに見えるこれ はあなたが選ぶ方法です
Jesus dear Lord Jesus I'm not perfect I
イエス様ご主人様イエス様私は 完璧で はあり ません私は
need a lot of help
たくさんの助けが必要
there's luck in my life and I realize I
私の人生には 運があり 、私は自分に気付いている
can't do it I need help would you help
それができない私は助けが必要です
me would you help me because it says
それが言うので私はあなたが私を助けてくれるでしょう
those who call and the name of the Lord
呼ぶ者と 主の 名
will be saved
保存されます
it says if we confess our sins he is
それは私たちが自分の罪を告白ならば、彼は言います
faithful and just to forgive us our sins
忠実で、ただ私たちの罪を許すために
and cleanse us of all unrighteousness
そしてすべての不義から私たちを清めてください
all not just some now just like the
すべての もの だけで はなく 、
little ones he is when we call
私達が呼ぶとき彼は小さい人
indistinct a believe us of all of it he
不明瞭な私たちはそれをすべて信じている
wipes the slate clean and as I want to
クリーンスレートを拭くと、私は し たいと
say it's just that easy and then it says
それは それほど簡単である と 言う そしてそれ から言う
to pick up your cross every day so it's
毎日あなたの十字架を拾うために
every day that's the cool thing is every
毎日クールなこと がすべてです
day so you start off right now the next
一日なので次は今すぐ始めます
five minutes dear God I don't really
5分 私は本当に神ではない
know what's new in the next five minutes
向こう5分の新着情報
but would you help me and you choose you
しかし 、あなたは私を助けてくれるだろうそしてあなたはあなたを選ぶ
choose to ask for his help and then I
彼の助け を求めること を 選び 、それから私は
want to say that he sort of have to step
彼はある種のステップをしなければならないと言いたい
back and just be amazed and how God's
バックだけ 驚かれること とどのように神の
going to bring people into your life how
どうやっ て人々 をあなたの人生 に連れて行きますか
through the power of the Holy Spirit
聖霊の力によって
he's going to change your words gonna
彼はあなたの言葉を変えるつもりです
change the way things you think you're
自分の考え を 変える
gonna change the way that you acted just
あなたの行動 の 仕方を 変えるつもりです
gonna say WOW god you're just that guy
WOWの神はあなたが ちょうどその 男だと言うつもり
we pray for us undershirt god you're
私たちはあなたの下にある 神の ために祈る
just that good you are just that good
ちょうどいいあなたはちょうど いい
and so lord help us to choose you every
だから 主は私たちがあなたを選ぶのを手伝ってくれる
day help us to choose you every day and
毎日あなたを選ぶのを助けて
Lord believe that you can do a wonderful
主はあなたが 素晴らしい ことができると信じています
work in our words and the way we listen
私たちの言葉で働き、私たちの 聞く方法
the way we feel the way we respond to
私たちが反応する 方法を感じる 方法
people or we don't want to we don't want
人や私たちはしたくない私たちはしたくない
to throw punch people you want to you
あなたにあなたが望む パンチ人を投げる
want to be patient you want to be quick
忍耐強く なりたい あなたは 早くなりたい
to hear you want to be slow to respond
あなたが応答するのが遅いことを望みます
you want to act with kindness and we
あなたは優しさと私たちを持って行動したいです
want to speak with truth or help us to
真実で話したい、または私たちを助けたい
communicate while we pray this in your
私たちがあなたの中でこれを祈っている間にコミュニケーションをとる
name Amen thank you so much for tuning
Amenさん 、チューニングありがとうございます。
in and really I feel the first seek
と 本当に私は最初のシークを感じる
first his kingdom and his righteousness
最初に彼の王国と彼の義
and all these things will be added to
そしてこれらすべてが追加されます
use
つかいます
that if you're seeking God then he's
もしあなたが神を求めているのなら、彼は
able to equip you with everything that
それをすべて装備することができます
you need to communicate in relationships
あなた は関係で 通信する必要があります
and that part in part comes through
そしてその一部は
worshiping him and I just want to put a
彼を崇拝しているだけで 、
link to the YouTube video for a song
曲の YouTube動画へのリンク
called seek first by the band bread and
バンドパンで最初にシークと呼ばれる
wine have a listen put it on give some
ワインが与えるいくつか の上に置く聞いてい
thought and and meet with the Lord so
思ったとし、 その 主と会います
thank you so much for tuning in we'll
我々はよで、チューニングのためにそんなに ありがとう
see you next week
また来週
catch a new episode of new everyday
新しい 毎日の新しいエピソードをキャッチ
every Friday morning at new every day
毎週金曜日の朝 、新しい毎日
dot TV
ドットテレビ
we're also on Kody Roku Plex YouTube and
私達はまたKody Roku Plex YouTubeにいます
Facebook or if you're in Southern
Facebook またはあなたがSouthernにいるなら
California tune in every Sunday morning
毎週日曜日の朝に カリフォルニアの 曲
at 6:30 Pacific on channel 33 television
6:30 Pacific at channel 33テレビ
for the high desert
砂漠のため